翻译校对       Mam
日  听      マキ
日听校对       Syura
翻译        葉隠
时间轴       乐小皓
压制       娜夏
诸神字幕组
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
"Kasanoda Syndicate"
- Good morning, Little Lord.
若　おはようございます
Yeah.
Little Lord, return to us safely.
若　行ってらっしゃいやし
- Return to us safely.
行ってらっしゃいやし
Yeah.
Little Lord, have
a good day at work today.
若　今日もお勤めご苦労さんです
- Have a good day at work today.
今日もお勤めご苦労さんです
"Ouran Academy High School
Class 1-D, Ritsu Kasanoda"
I'm always telling ya, don't
call my going to school "work"!
いつも言ってるだろう
学校行くの　お勤めっつうんじゃねえ
- Pardon us!
失礼いたしやした
Little Lord, your car?
若　お車は
That's okay. Starting today,
I'm going to walk for a while.
いい　今日から暫く歩いていく
を掛けられるな
Tetsuya, I'm surprised that ya'd speak
to Little Lord like that just then.
Little Lord's glaring power's
gotten even more scary lately.
若の眼力　最近更におっかねえよな
あれはゼッテー学校で誰かムカつく野郎でもいるに違ぇねえよ
That's no doubt 'cause
there's some bastard at school
he's got a beef with.
今日こそその日だぜ
Today is the day...
... Morinozkuka Takashi.
銛之塚崇
"After school"
- Welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
"Ikeda Shop"
"The Host Club is now open for business"
Tamaki- kun, you're dressed
as Sakamoto Ryoma, right?
環くんは坂本龍馬のご衣装ですのね
Wild and handsome!
ワイルドで格好いい
Yeah. I'm gon' make sure
I get your hearts, too.
ああ　おまんらハートはこん俺が必ずゲットしちゃるきに
土佐弁の環くんも素敵
Tamaki- kun, it's so fantastic
when you speak in Tosa dialect!
いや　おかしいでしょう　そこだけ土佐弁とかって
No, it's weird, just speaking
Tosa dialect where he did.
Still, I didn't know that late-Edo
era cosplay would be this popular.
でも知らなかったな　幕末コスプレって受けがいいんだ
What are you talking about?
That's one of the basics of the basics.
何言ってんの　基本中の基本でしょう
There are more girls that like the
late Edo era than you can imagine.
幕末大好き女子は想像以上に多いんだよ
Especially the Shinsengumi.
特に新選組ね
ともかく　好きな子にはマニアさんが多いよね
And in any case, among those who like it,
there are lots of real maniacs.
Perhaps the reason for their
popularity was their gallantry
その人気の理由が若くして国のために散った気高さにあるのか
in giving their young lives
for the sake of the country.
ひたすらに武士道を貫き　自らを律したストイックさにあるのか
In their single-mindedness
to live the bushido code,
and in the stoic way in which
they comported themselves.
"Maniac"
Or perhaps...
それとも…
Don't you die.
死ぬな
私はもう　ダメだ
I'm done for.
ギムナジウム的な男子集団に禁断の香りを感じるのか
...they detect the scent
of something forbidden,
coming from this gymnázein
group of young men.
The Ikeda-ya Inn may indeed
be generally well-known,
やっぱり一般的には池田屋があまりにも有名ですけれど
but for me, just imagining
the back of Hijikata- san,
私としては鳥伏見後の北の大地に向かって
facing the northern lands,
following the battle at Tobafushimi,
一人新選組を守り抜こうとする
土方さんの哀愁漂う背中を想像するだけで
sorrowfully wandering, trying
to defend the Shinsengumi by himself,
I could eat three whole bowls of rice!
ご飯３杯はいけますわ
Renge-chan sure does
cover a lot of territory.
蓮華ちゃん　守備範囲広いなあ
Following your advice
to not have us cast ourselves
下手にこちらで特定の役のキャステイングをやらずに
in any specific roles,
saying it would be better
お客さんの自由な妄想にお任せする方がいいという
to leave it up to our guests
to freely fantasize for themselves,
君のアドバイスは正解だったよ
was the right choice.
Naturally. Still,
当然ですわ
でも　やっぱり沖田総司はハルヒくんで決まり
sure enough, having Haruhi- kun
be Okita Soji is perfect.
He does indeed fit in as the handsome,
evanescent young swordsman!
まさに儚げな美少年剣士よねえ
"Freely fantasizing"
No, Haruhi- kun, don't die!
いや　ハルヒくん　死なないで
Today, they're having a bargain
sale on pork at the supermarket.
今日　スーパーで豚肉の特売があるんだけど　間に合うかな
"Her thoughts aren't all
that evanescent, though"
Can I make it there in time?
Mori- kun has to be Shimada Kai, huh?
モリくんはやっぱり島田魁よね
Huh? Yamazaki- san would be better.
ええ　山崎さんがいいわよ
My dark horse choice would be Soma- san.
私は大穴で相馬さんが
Mori- senpai!
モリ先輩
Why the sudden lunge!?
どったの　急に
Discontent about not
getting any attention?
目立たないから　不満？
Mori- senpai, please calm down!
モリ先輩　落ち着いてください
毎回セリフが一言しかない上
I know that not only do you get
only one line every episode,
２クール目の後半だと言うのに
but that it's also the last
half of our second half-season,
見せ場のエピソードが少なくて苛立つのはよくわかりますが
and that you haven't had
many showcase episodes,
so you must be irritated...
違う
No.
We have a trespasser.
不法侵入者だ
銛之塚崇
Morinozuka Takashi!
討ち入り
- Surprise attack!?
Senpai! Please take me
on as your apprentice!
先輩　俺を弟子にしてください
···ハア？
- Huh?
Kasanoda Ritsu,
of 1st year, Class D.
一年D組　笠野田律
Heir to the 3rd-generation
head of the Kasanoda Syndicate,
関東圏のその筋で最大の力を持つ笠野田組三代目の跡取り息子
the most powerful line
in the whole Kanto area.
Admitted to Ouran for high school.
桜蘭には高等部より入学
Long red hair and
a mean-looking appearance;
赤いロン毛と凶悪な目つき　無口で友人なし
taciturn, and without friends.
If your eyes meet, you will have
bad dreams for three months;
目が合えば相手に三ヶ月は悪夢を見せ
if you bump shoulders,
you will be sent to the hospital;
肩にぶつかれば病院送り
those who attempt to talk back to him
are sent directly to their graves.
口答えしようものなら　墓場へ直行
そしてクラスメートには人間ブリザードとして恐れられている
Also, he is feared by his
classmates as "the human blizzard."
"Those who approach him
are frozen over"
So, why does a human
weapon like yourself
それで　そんな人間凶器の君がなぜモリ先輩に弟子入りを
want to become an apprentice
of Mori- senpai?
That's not true.
I am not a human weapon.
違う　俺は人間凶器なんかじゃねえ
俺はただ生まれつき目つきが凶悪なだけなんだ
I was just born with a face
that makes me look mean.
Then you're aware of it, Casanova- kun.
自覚はあるんだ　カサノバくん
It's Kasanoda!
笠野田だ
Bossa Nova?
ボサノバ？
笠野田っつってんだろう　死にてえのか
I said it was Kadanoda!!
You wanna die!?
He does indeed have a mean look.
確かに凶悪な目つきだ
Damn it...
チクショウ
この目つきのために俺は
It's all because of the way I look.
From the time I was born,
since I was just a tyke,
生まれたときからこの凶悪な目つきで
my old man would always say
'cause of this mean look I have...
小さい頃からオヤジにはよく言われた
He's set to be the greatest
gangster of our time.
こいつは今世紀最大の極道になる器だ
Little Lord, are you going to a rumble?
若　出入りで
- Little Lord, are you going to a rumble?
And so, from the time I was little,
I was taught how to be a godfather.
そして  子供の頃から極道の帝王学を学ばされた
Do not be too friendly when talking
to others. They'll look down on you.
気安く人に話しかけるな　嘗められる
Yeah.
"Ah"
It's not "yeah,"
「ああ」じゃない　「あ゛あ゛」だ
it's "yeah!!" Now you read it.
読んでみろ
あ゛あ゛あ゛あ゛
"Yeah!!"
Good. Nice and gangsterish.
よし　極道っぽいぞ
次はこれだ
Next, try this.
"Ma"
Ma!
That's not a gangster, that's
something-or-other-Robo, ain't it!?
それは極道じゃなくて　なんとかロボだろう
When am I ever going to use that word!?
そんな言葉　とこで使うんだよ
とにかく　その極道教育のおかげで
Anyhow, thanks to that
gangster's education,
人はみんな寄り付けず
nobody ever comes near me.
Even my fellas got scared,
and won't get too close anymore.
舎弟さえも俺を恐れて近付かなくなった
And so, I am all alone.
そして　俺は孤独だった
But really, I, too, would like
to play with everyone else.
けど　本当は俺だってみんなと遊びたい
I'd like to play kick the can
with the fellas that follow me.
慕ってくれる舎弟達と一緒に缶けりとかしたいんだ
To be sure, playing kick the can is nice.
確かに　缶けりはいいよな
But I don't know how
I'm supposed to associate
けど　今更どうやって人と関わったらいいか　分かんねえんだよ
with other people anymore.
Poor guy.
可哀想
Morinozuka- senpai,
that's why I need you to show me.
銛之塚先輩　だから教えて欲しい
なんであんたはそんなふうなのか
How can you be the way you are?
As mean-looking as you are?
そんなに目つきが悪くて
Expressionless, unspeaking,
and unsociable,
無表情で無口で無愛想で
you've got a mug like the watchdog
from hell, so how is it
十分地獄の番犬みたいなツラしてんのに
どうしたらそんなにまわりの奴らに慕われることができるのか
that you're able to get those who
are around you to like you so much?
Please, teach me
どうかその秘訣を俺に
your secrets!
Takashi, are you okay?
崇　大丈夫
I'm a little lightheaded.
少しめまいが
Sir...
殿
...are you sure we
shouldn't do anything?
なんとかしなくていいわけ？
No, leave him be.
ダメだ　放っておけ
He said that he wanted to become
Mori- senpai's apprentice.
彼はモリ先輩に弟子入りしたいと言っている
Mori- senpai must be the one
who decides what to do.
どうするか決めるのは　モリ先輩だ
This is not something that
we can interfere with.
俺たちが口を挟んでいいことじゃない
Tamaki...
環
"Help."
いいでしょう　モリ先輩がそこまでおっしゃるなら
Very well. Mori- senpai,
if you insist, I, Suou Tamaki,
この須王環　及ばずならが　一肌脱がせて頂きましょう
will do whatever little
I can to help you out.
Actually, you wanted to get involved
so badly, you couldn't bear it, huh?
本当は手を出したくて仕方なかったんだな
Lift your head, Bossa Nova- kun.
顔を上げろ　ボサノバくん
It's Kasanoda.
笠野田です
For the time being, you can
call me King, Bossa Nova- kun.
俺のことは仮にキングと呼ぶがいい　ボサノバくん
I told you...
だから…
Are you listening,
Bossa Nova- kun?
いいかね　ボサノバくん
Yes, sir.
There may be many points of difference
between you and Mori- senpai,
君とモリ先輩の相違点は多々あれど
but there is one definitive
thing that you are lacking.
決定的に君に欠けているものが一つある
That being, a lovely item!
それは　ラブリーアイテムだ
Lovely... item?
ラブリーアイテム
I would now like
to introduce to you this...
今回ご紹介するのはこちら　ラブリーアイテム光邦くんである
...lovely item, "Mitsukuni- kun."
Sure, maybe Mori- senpai
does have a mean look,
確かにモリ先輩は一見　目つきが悪く冷たい印象かもしれん
and gives off a feeling
of iciness at first glance.
But what if we put this
"Mitsukuni- kun" atop his shoulders?
ところが　この光邦くんを肩に載せればどうだ
It's almost like he's a forest teddy-bear
that little animals are fond of.
まるで小動物に好かれる森の熊さん状態
In addition, this item also plays up
Mori- senpai's tight-lipped character.
更に　このアイテムはモリ先輩の無口キャラをもフォローしてしまう
Even without saying anything,
just by placing Honey- senpai with him
何を語らずとも　ハニー先輩を配置するだけで
people discover a tolerance for
Mori- senpai all on their own,
人は勝手にモリ先輩に包容力を見出し
and they are left with
a positive interpretation of him
寡黙な好青年とポジテイブ解釈させてしまうという寸法なのだ
as a nice, quiet young man.
That's the plan.
"The plan"
It's no exaggeration to say
that Mori- senpai's charm
ハニー先輩がいてはじめて
モリ先輩の魅力が確立するといっっても過言ではないだろう
was first established once
Honey- senpai was there.
- Indeed, you're right.
なるほど
Now that you mention it,
Mori- senpai...
そういえば　モリ先輩って
基本何もしてない
...basically doesn't do anything.
His position is a big "bzzt?"
ポジション的にブー？
Takashi...
崇
僕のこと利用してたの？
Were you just using me?
But "Mitsukuni- kun" is on long-term
contract to Mori- senpai,
だが光邦くんはモリ先輩が長期契約されているから
so you cannot borrow him.
君には貸せない
Have I been rented to you, Takashi!?
僕　崇にレンタルされてるの？
Well, I'll think of something
to take his place.
ま　何か替わるものを考えよう
The next thing to address
あと　問題にすべきは
is your "yankee" fashion.
そのヤンキーファッションだな
"Yankee fashion!"
Hitachiin Brothers...
常陸院ブラザーズ
Sir!
Come up with an image change
for this man's fashion.
この者のファッションをイメチェンせよ
Roger!
了解
"Kasanoda Syndicate"
Good work, Tetsuya.
ご苦労だな　鉄也
Ah, Little Lord, welcome home.
若　お帰りなせえやし
"Lovely item"
Little Lord, welcome home.
- Welcome home.
お帰りなせえやし
Yeah.
Little Lord, what's going on?
若　どうなすったんで　学校で何か
Did something happen at school?
"Incredibly embarrassed"
Little Lord...
若
Damn it all! This is completely
wrong, ain't it!?
チクショウ　全然ダメじゃねえか
Why, those miserable...
あいつらめ
さっきのは笠野田組四代目の小僧か
So that kid just now
was the 4th head of
the Kasanoda Syndicate?
What do we do? We can't very well
go bustin' into their estate.
どうする　さすがに屋敷に乗り込むわけにはいかねえぞ
We'll get him at school tomorrow.
Gotta make sure he pays
明日学校でやる
この落とし前は　きっちり付けてもらわねえとな
for what he's done.
The weather's turning bad.
Looks like it's going to rain.
天気悪い　降りそうだな
Huh? Did Little Lord take
an umbrella with him?
あれ　若　傘持って行ったっけ
aniki: "brother"
Aniki Morinozuka,
銛之塚の兄貴　おはようございます
good morning.
おはよう　ボサノバくん
Good morning, Bossa Nova- kun.
Hey there, Haninozuka- senpai!
ウス　埴之塚先輩
Hey there...
I will carry your bag
to the classroom for you.
教室までカバンをお持ちします
いい　間に合ってる
That's okay, I can manage.
What is it!?
なんすか
Mori- kun, are you hurt?
モリくん　お怪我は
大丈夫か　銛之塚
Are you okay, Morinozuka?
Who on earth could have done this?
一体誰がこんなことを
Are you all right?
大丈夫
Yeah.
He's incredibly well-liked.
Even as scary as he looks.
すげえ慕われてる
あんなに目つき怖いのに
No, this ain't no time
to be going on about that...
いや　そんなこと言ってる場合じゃねえ
Huh? Someone is out to get Mori- senpai?
はあ　モリ先輩が狙われてる
"Music Room #3"
No doubt about it.
I was there when it happened.
間違いねえ　俺は現場に居合わせたんだ
Clearly, he's gotten on
the wrong side of someone.
明らかに誰かの恨みを買ってる
Oh, no way, no way.
Mori- senpai would be the last person
to get on someone's wrong side.
モリ先輩に限って　恨みを買うとかはない
You don't know that for sure!
分かんねえだろう　そんなこと
Never mind that, Bossa Nova- kun,
そんなことより　ボサノバくん
"The 'Turn Bossa Nova
into an Angel' Project"
as of today, we start "Operation
Bossa Nova- kun Image-up" in earnest!
本日より　ボサノバくんイメージアップ作戦を本格的に開始する
- Yes, sir!
イェッサー
Hey, just a minute!
What do you mean, "as of today"!?
ちょっと待って！オイ！
本日よりってなんだよ　昨日のあれをなかったことにすんじゃねえ
Don't go pretending that thing
yesterday didn't happen!
Thanks to that, people were even more
afraid of me yesterday than usual.
アレのせいで　俺は昨日　普段より余計恐れられちまったんだ
Bossa Nova- kun, I hope
you don't misunderstand.
ボサノバくん　誤解しないでほしい
We really are behind you on this.
俺たちは本気で君を応援している
That thing yesterday was just the twins
getting a little carried away.
昨日のは　あの双子のちょっとした勇み足だ
"You bear no responsibility?"
許してやってほしい
I hope you'll forgive them.
They really are behind me?
本気で応援？
Sorry. I am in your hands.
すんません　よろしくお願いします
All right, does anyone have any ideas?
よーし　さあ　誰か意見を　意見を言いなさい
Um, Casanova- kun...
あのう　カサノバくん
あんまりあの人達の言うことを信じすぎない方がいいよ
You're better off not putting too much
faith into what those guys say.
"Well-meaning tip-off"
But they were recommended
to me by Aniki Morinozuka.
だけど　銛之塚の兄貴の推薦した人たちだし
Besides, I'm the one who's imposing,
and asking a lot of them.
それに無理言って迷惑かけてんのはこっちだし
あれ　そういや　あんた　誰だっけ
Huh? Come to think of it, who are you?
Fujioka. We're both 1st-Years.
同じ一年の藤岡です
I was also admitted once
I got to high school.
自分も高等部からの入学なんだ
I guess that makes us mates.
仲間だね
Mates...
仲間
D-do you like playing kick the can?
あ　あんた　缶けりとか好きか
Well... if I had to say,
I'm probably not too interested.
さあ　どちらかっていうと　興味ないかも
Still...
でも　たまにはいいかもね
it might be fun, once in a while.
What?
He's a lot like a chick.
女みてえなやつだな
Bossa Nova- kun!
ボサノバくん
Yes?
We've decided on a strategy
for your lovely image.
君のラブリーイメージ戦略が決定したよ
He's a cat-monster.
化け猫
That's strange. I was told
by Renge- kun that these days,
おかしいなあ　猫耳は昨今かなりの万能ラブリーアイテムであると
kitty ears are quite
the do-it-all lovely item.
蓮華君から教えられていたのだが
Well, naturally, there are limits
to what placing ears on him
ま　つけ耳だけで　目つきの恐ろしさを緩和させるのには
can do, to temper the frightfulness
of his appearance.
自ずと限界がある
Sir, that came off pretty weak.
殿は詰めが甘いんだよ
Yeah, yeah. If you're going
to do it at all, then look...
そうそう　どうせやるならほら
...you've got to go all the way,
and make him a kitty-eared maid.
思い切って猫耳メードさんにしないと
Are you guys making fun of me?
嘗めてんのか　テメエら
Excuse me, is Little
Lord Kasanoda in here?
失礼しやす　笠野田の若はこちらに
すまなかっ
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt your private pastime.
すいやせん　密やかなご趣味の最中に
"Embarrassed"
Who are you saying has
a private pastime!? Damn it!
誰にや密やかな趣味だ
くそ　もうやってらんねえよ
I can't take this anymore!
Little Lord! Little Lord!
若　若
But really, I, too, would like
to play with everyone else.
けど　本当は俺だってみんなと遊びたい
I'd like to play kick the can
with the fellas that follow me.
慕ってくれる舎弟達と一緒に缶けりとかしたいんだ
I wonder if Casanova- kun
really needs an image change.
カサノバくんにイメチェンなんて必要なのかな
Yeah, you're right.
そうだね
I sure hope he realizes it soon.
早く気づくといいね
Kasanoda-kun is always
in such a bad mood.
笠野田くんっていつも機嫌悪いよね
Yeah, he scares me.
やだ　怖い
They say not to look him in the eye.
目　合わせんなって
Why am I always so...
なんでいつも俺は…
Look, I brought you something to eat.
ほら　餌持ってきてやったぞ
Let me see how that wing is doing.
の具合見せてみろ
Oh, it's looking all right now.
もう大丈夫そうだな
ああ　雀
Ah, a sparrow.
Eh? What are you doing here?
お前　なんでここに
What happened to your sparrow?
その雀　どうしたの
この間　ここで怪我して落ちてたんだ
It got hurt, and had fallen
down here the other day.
I took it to a doctor, who said
it would heal in no time.
医者に連れてったら　じきに治るって
Can I give it some food?
餌　あげてもいい
Y-yeah...
Fujioka. We're both 1st-Years.
I guess that makes us mates.
同じ一年の藤岡です
仲間だね
Now that I notice it, this guy
don't seem all that afraid of me.
そういやこいつ　あんまり俺のこと　怖がんねえな
What huge, dark eyes he's got.
So sparkly. He really is like a chick.
でかい黒目だな　キラキラしてる　ホント女みたい
Chicks are especially afraid of me,
女なんて　特に俺のこと怖がるから
so I've never been able
to talk to one like this.
今までこんなふうに喋ったことも
って　男だろうが　こいつは
But he's a guy!
What am I thinking!?
何考えてんだ　俺は！
危ない
Look out!
It flew away.
飛んだ
H-Haruhi, are you all right!?
ハ　ハルヒ　無事か
Is that blood!?
それは血か
No, I just got some
paint on me, that's all.
いいえ　ペンキがかかっただけです
Are you sure you're all right, Fujioka?
本当に大丈夫か　藤岡
Mm-hmm.
Let go of me, you bastard!
離せこのやろう
You big behemoth!
このデカブツめ
汚ねえぞ　笠野田
This is dirty of you, Kasanoda!
Not only do you kidnap our boss's kid,
うちの頭の坊ちゃんを攫ったあげく
you're also using
musclemen like this one!
こんな用心棒まで用意しやがって
この誘拐魔め　坊ちゃんを返せ
You rotten kidnapper!
Give us back the kid!
Silence, you ruffians!
Here's some rope!
黙れ曲者　お縄じゃ
What's this about?
何の話だ
You know what?
あのね　狙われてたのは最初からボサノバくんだったんだよ
You were the one they were
after all along, Bossa Nova- kun.
犯人が捕まるまで黙ってることにしたの
We decided not to say anything
until we caught the culprits.
To avoid having any
disturbance, you know?
騒動にならないようにね
So then, you helped me?
俺のこと　助けてくれたのですか
Why?
なんで
We can tell just by looking
who the bad guys are.
どちらが悪人かは見ればわかる
I'm going to go change my clothes.
自分　ちょっと着替えてきます
Need some help?
手伝おうか
No thanks.
結構です
You dumbasses!
バカ野郎
Sonny!
坊ちゃん
逆恨みも大概にしろ
That's enough of your misplaced blame!
Don't you get it yet that I left
テメエらみてえなのといんのがいやで出て行ったのが
because I was sick of hanging
with the likes of you!?
まだ分かんねえのか
Get lost already, will ya!?
とっとと失せやがれ
鉄也　テメエは
Tetsuya, you're...
I'm terribly sorry for not telling you.
黙っていて　申し訳ありやせんでした
I am Sendo Tetsuya, son of the godfather
自分は千堂組関東支部組長の息子　千堂鉄也と申しやす
of the Kanto branch
of the Sendo Syndicate.
I have long been opposed
to the any-means-necessary
俺は兼ねてより　千堂組の手段を選ばぬやり方に反発してて
methods of the Sendo Syndicate,
and at length,
one rainy day, a year ago,
一年前のある雨の日　ついにオヤジと大喧嘩して
I got into a big blowup
with my old man,
家を飛び出したんです
and ran away from home.
あんな不安な気持ちになったのは初めてでした
I'd never felt as anxious
before as I did then.
I had nowhere to go,
and everyone else along the street
行く宛もなく
道行く人がみんな俺なんてまるで見えないように通り過ぎていく
just passed by me, as though
they couldn't even see me.
そんな時　若が
Just then, Little Lord...
Little Lord, you're exactly
the sort of person I thought you'd be
若は　あの時俺が一目見て思ったとおりの人です
when I first saw you.
Afterward, when I went to join
up with the Kasanoda Syndicate,
あの後　笠野田組に押し掛けていった俺を優しく向かい入れてくれて
you accepted me with kindness.
俺は知ってやす
I know, Little Lord,
that you're more self-conscious
若が人一倍照れやで不器用で
and awkward than most people, and yet,
それでも　人一倍あったけえってことを
you're warmer than most people.
And it's not just me.
Everyone in the syndicate knows.
俺だけじゃない　組のもんはみんな知ってやす
They just don't say anything,
since it would embarrass you.
若が恥ずかしがるから言えないだけなんです
I, Sendo Tetsuya, wished to be
someone like you, Little Lord,
この千堂鉄也　若の人柄に惚れ　千堂組とは縁を切り
so I cut my ties with the Sendo
Syndicate, and consigned myself
笠野田組に骨を埋める覚悟でございやす
to make my home among
the Kasanoda Syndicate.
Please, allow me to remain
at your side, Little Lord,
俺を　これからも若の傍に置いてやってくだせえ
from here on out, as well.
あ　そうだ　これを
Oh, right...
Here.
The weather is turning bad,
so please keep this.
天気悪いんで　お持ちくだせえ
If our 4th were to get a cold,
everyone would worry.
四代目が風邪でもこじらせたりしたら　みんな心配しやすんで
You guys...
オメエら
l-I will use it, then.
使わせてもらう
Right.
What a great story! I'm touched!
いい話だ　感動
Oh, I should apologize to Fujioka.
俺　藤岡に謝んねえと
It's 'cause of me that
he got paint all over him.
俺のせいでペンキまみれにさせちまった
Haru-chan went to
the club room, to change.
ハルちゃんなら　部室に着替えに行ったよ
あ　どうも　行ってくる
Oh, thanks.
I'll be right back.
Right. Oh, Little Lord!
Let's play kick the can later!
あ　若　後で缶蹴り致しやしょう
Yeah!
We've done a good thing here.
良いことをした
Sir, you didn't do anything
this time, did you?
今回殿は何もしてないじゃん
More importantly, doesn't anyone care?
そんなことより　いいのか
Haruhi went to go change clothes.
ハルヒは「着替え」に行ったんだぞ
Ma!!
"Music Room #3"
Fujioka?
藤岡
Huh? Is he in the prep room?
あれ　準備室か
Fujioka?
藤岡　大丈夫か　悪かったな
You okay? I'm sorry about-
あ　ちょっと
Hey!
M-
Ma-
"Ma!!"
Ma!!
Bossa Nova-chi is coming
to the Host Club now, as a guest!
ボサノバっちがホスト部にお客できてる
What's more, he's asking for Haruhi!
しかもハルヒをご指名だぞ
このままハルヒがボサノバっちに迫られたら
If Bossa Nova-chi starts chasing
after Haruhi like this...
Sir, do something!
殿　何とかしてよ
Next time,
"Tamaki's Unwitting Depression"
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ　来週も
Ouran High School Host Club
does not need any male
guests coming in next week!
男の客は来なくていい！！